collectorsweekly.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Collectors Weekly

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Collectorsweekly.com. We are committed to respecting your online privacy and to protecting and appropriately managing any personal information you share with us. Personal Information means any information that can be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, personal profile, a home or work or other physical address, and an email address or other contact information. We value your trust. Please take a moment to read through this privacy policy. This privacy policy forms part of the Terms of Use.

#### Information We Collect

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the site, for example to ask a question, request more information, or respond to a survey, we do not currently provide this Personal Information to third parties. However, information, including Personal Information, that we collect from you is considered to be a business asset. Thus, if we are acquired by a third party as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale or if our assets are acquired by a third party in the event we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, may be disclosed or transferred to a third party acquirer in connection with the transaction. We may also share aggregated demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregated information will not contain any Personal Information that can identify an individual user.

#### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our site pages may utilize “cookies” or other tracking technologies. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.

#### Security

We have implemented suitable security policies to protect and safeguard the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

#### Links and Third-Party Websites

Our Site may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. Our website may also use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at our website. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

#### Your Consent

By using this website you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our website. We reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our website following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

#### Contact

If you have any comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact@collectorsweekly.com.
